secretgeek.net 2012-12-23

# Privacy Policy

## Relax

I do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies. I keep your information secure, so that no known viruses, worms, spiders or other nasties can steal your email adress or other information.

I abhor spam.

I gather traffic information on an anonymous basis and exclusively use this for analysing the effectiveness of my site. I don't make this information available to anyone else. I don't use 'Web Bugs' or other tricks.

The site now contains advertisements. In particular there are 'google ads' down the right hand side of the page. In future I might put these ads in a more prominent location, since you slackers don't seem to click on them often enough. A contract with google prevents me from disclosing how much money I make from the ads. I think it's okay for me to admit this much though: to date it's not enough to cover hosting costs.

I also use the 'Amazon Referer' program in a futile attempt to make serious money. When I mention a book I sometimes provide a link to "Amazon.com." If such a link contains the word 'secretGeek' then you can be certain I'm out to make a few bucks on the quick. I only recommend books that I actually like, though, so if I say "Go and buy this book" then it's motivated by one part greed and one part honesty. If I were a little less greedy I would say "Go and borrow this book from a library." I like libraries and I think more people should use them.

Also, publishers send me books, gratis, and I review them here. I only publish review for book that I like, or that I find interesting. This is an offshoot of my general philosophy: If you can't think of anything nice to say, then shut the f*ck up. You should know that at least a small part of my honesty in these reviews must be affected by my bibliophilic wish to keep getting free books. Still, I'm proud to encourage people to read books. Books are better than web sites. Go read one now.

If you wish, you may request a copy of any personal information which I hold about you at any time. If you are aware of any inaccuracies in such personal information then I will take any steps necessary to correct those inaccuracies. I can destroy any private information I hold about you, If you so choose. 

If you have any concerns about this privacy policy, please contact me. 

Add or view comments about this page

|   Harvey, a .net chat server built with RabbitMQ  
 LeonBambrick.com  
 So your domain has been stolen. What now?  
 kv can remember it for you, wholesale  
 Hello IT Department  
 Dialog Between a Man and His Vista Laptop  
 NimbleText 1.6, Codename Jetboat  
 On Task Hoarding and Todo Bankruptcy  
 Developer UI Done Right: Mercurial Commandline!  
 Rediscovering the Amstrad CPC 6128  
 Just Wally  
 The Correct Order for a First Time Viewing of The Lord Of The Rings  
 A new era for Android.  
 Mind-boggling Demo of New Gaming Genre, aka Folder-Based Hangman, aka Fun with Recursion  
 Got CSV in your javascript? Use agnes.  

* * *

 Complete secretGeek Archives  

* * *

* * *

 25 steps for building a Micro-ISV  
 3 Minute Guide Series  
 Universal Troubleshooting Checklist  
 Top 10 SecretGeek articles  
[ ShinyPower  
Now at CodePlex](http://www.codeplex.com/Wiki/View.aspx?ProjectName=ShinyPower)  

* * *

* * *

* * *

 How to be depressed  

* * *

* * *

### Recommended Reading

[  
the little schemer](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0262560992/ref=as_li_tf_tl?ie=UTF8&tag=secretgeek-20&linkCode=as2&camp=217145&creative=399377&creativeASIN=0262560992 "the little schemer")

* * *

### Recommended blogs

* * *

### Aggregated Links

* * *

### Human Link Machines

* * *

* * *
